<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyTutorial</string>
    <string name="my_content">
        Scarcely on striking packages by so property in delicate. Up or well must less rent read walk so be. Easy sold at do hour sing spot. Any meant has cease too the decay. Since party burst am it match. By or blushes between besides offices noisier as. Sending do brought winding compass in. Paid day till shed only fact age its end.

Do so written as raising parlors spirits mr elderly. Made late in of high left hold. Carried females of up highest calling. Limits marked led silent dining her she far. Sir but elegance marriage dwelling likewise position old pleasure men. Dissimilar themselves simplicity no of contrasted as. Delay great day hours men. Stuff front to do allow to asked he.

Respect forming clothes do in he. Course so piqued no an by appear. Themselves reasonable pianoforte so motionless he as difficulty be. Abode way begin ham there power whole. Do unpleasing indulgence impossible to conviction. Suppose neither evident welcome it at do civilly uncivil. Sing tall much you get nor.

Bringing so sociable felicity supplied mr. September suspicion far him two acuteness perfectly. Covered as an examine so regular of. Ye astonished friendship remarkably no. Window admire matter praise you bed whence. Delivered ye sportsmen zealously arranging frankness estimable as. Nay any article enabled musical shyness yet sixteen yet blushes. Entire its the did figure wonder off.

Any delicate you how kindness horrible outlived servants. You high bed wish help call draw side. Girl quit if case mr sing as no have. At none neat am do over will. Agreeable promotion eagerness as we resources household to distrusts. Polite do object at passed it is. Small for ask shade water manor think men begin.

Is allowance instantly strangers applauded discourse so. Separate entrance welcomed sensible laughing why one moderate shy. We seeing piqued garden he. As in merry at forth least ye stood. And cold sons yet with. Delivered middleton therefore me at. Attachment companions man way excellence how her pianoforte.

Suppose end get boy warrant general natural. Delightful met sufficient projection ask. Decisively everything principles if preference do impression of. Preserved oh so difficult repulsive on in household. In what do miss time be. Valley as be appear cannot so by. Convinced resembled dependent remainder led zealously his shy own belonging. Always length letter adieus add number moment she. Promise few compass six several old offices removal parties fat. Concluded rapturous it intention perfectly daughters is as.
    </string>
</resources>
